# Carla Prida

# Graphic Designer



### Hello!

I'm a Dominican/Spanish graphic designer living in Barcelona. Inspired by the greatness in simple things. I strive to understand how great design works, and try to challenge myself daily. Specialized in branding, editorial, and web design.

Date of Birth: April 30th, 1993 Nationality: Dominican / Spanish Resides in: Barcelona, Spain

+34 663 763 009 carla.prida@gmail.com www.carlaprida.com Behance /carlaprida Instagram /carlaprida Available to start whenever!

### Languages

Spanish / native
English / fluent
French / basic
HTML / intermediate
CSS / intermediate

# Personal Skills

Flexible & Adaptable
Responsible
Queen of Computer Shortcuts
Thrives in teamwork
Can talk to anyone or anything

# Design Skills

llustrator	
ndesign	
Photoshop	
After Effects	
Sketch	

# Education

M.A. Graphic Design Elisava Barcelona, Spain / 2015-2016

B.A. Advertising

Michigan State University

East Lansing, Michigan / 2011-2015

Graphic Design Course

Yale University, Summer Program

New Haven, Connecticut / 2010

Advertising & Marketing Course Yale University, Summer Program New Haven, Connecticut / 2010

# Experience

Graphic Designer

DomésticoShop

Barcelona, Spain / 2017 – currently

Design Intern Bisgràfic Barcelona, Spain / 2016

Designer
The State News
East Lansing, Michigan / 2014-2015

Community Manager + Designer Liquid Digital Agency Santo Domingo, Dom. Rep. / 2014

Design Intern
Partners Ogilvy & Mather
Santo Domingo, Dom. Rep. / 2013

Junior Designer

Contacto Advertising Agency

Santo Domingo, Dom. Rep. / 2012

Design Intern

Pages BBDO Advertising Agency Santo Domingo, Dom. Rep. / 2011

# Honors & Awards

Full Scholarship

Awarded a full scholarship for my bachelor's degree at Michigan State University from the DR's Ministy of Higher Education / 2011-2015

Four ADDY'S

American Advertising Awards (AAF). Regional winner of one silver and three bronze ADDYs / 2015

# Carla Prida



### iHola!

Soy una diseñadora gráfica que busca inspiración en la grandeza de las cosas simples. Me esfuerzo por entender cómo funciona un gran diseño y trato de desafiarme a mí misma diariamente. Especializada en branding, diseño web y editorial.

Nacimiento: 30 de Abril, 1993 Nacionalidad: Dominicana/Española Residente: Barcelona, España

+34 663 763 009 carla.prida@gmail.com www.carlaprida.com Behance /carlaprida Instagram /carlaprida Disponibilidad inmediata

#### Idiomas

Castellano / nativo Inglés / fluido Francés / basico HTML / intermedio CSS / intermedio

### Destrezas

Flexible & Adaptable
Responsable
Reina de los comandos de Adobe
Próspera en trabajo en equipo
Puede tener una conversación con
cualquier persona o cosa

### Destrezas Diseño

Illustrator	
Indesign	
· ·	
Photoshop	
After Effects	
Skotch	

# Educación

M.A. Diseño Gráfico Elisava Barcelona, España / 2015-2016

B.A. Publicidad Michigan State University East Lansing, Michigan / 2011-2015

Curso de Diseño Gráfico Yale University, Summer Program New Haven, Connecticut / 2010

Curso de Publicidad & Marketing Yale University, Summer Program New Haven, Connecticut / 2010

# Experiencia

Diseñadora Gráfica

DomésticoShop

Barcelona, España / actualmente

Prácticas – Diseñadora

Bisgràfic

Barcelona, España / 2016

Diseñadora

The State News East Lansing, Michigan / 2014-2015

Community Manager + Diseñadora Liquid Digital Agency Santo Domingo, Rep. Dom. / 2014

Prácticas –Diseñadora Partners Ogilvy & Mather Santo Domingo, Rep. Dom. / 2013 Diseñadora Junior

Contacto Advertising Agency Santo Domingo, Rep. Dom. / 2012

Prácticas –Diseñadora

Pages BBDO Advertising Agency Santo Domingo, Rep. Dom. / 2011

### Honores & Premios

Beca Completa

Otorgada una beca completa para grado en Michigan State University por el Ministerio de Educación de la República Dominicana / 2011-2015

Cuatro ADDY'S

American Advertising Awards (AAF). Ganadora regional de cuatro ADDYs, uno plata y tres bronces / 2015